[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first rule of the fictional Fight Club is you do not talk about Fight Club. What is the second rule of Fight Club?", "correct_answer": "You DO NOT talk about Fight Club", "incorrect_answers": ["Only two guys to a fight", "One fight at a time", "If its your first night at Fight Club, you have to fight."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Arabian dish Manakish is very similar to this very popular Italian food.", "correct_answer": "Pizza", "incorrect_answers": ["Lasagna", "Spaghetti", "Ravioli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Blood Diamond, this character, played by Djimon Hounsou, is the man who finds the enormous diamond.", "correct_answer": "Solomon Vandy", "incorrect_answers": ["Solomon Dia", "Nabil Cullins", "Cordell NDail"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following should be avoided in the pet chinchillas diet?", "correct_answer": "Fresh vegetables", "incorrect_answers": ["Hay", "Water", "Raisin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Breakfast Club, Allison gives Bender one of her diamond earrings.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Coca-Cola used to contain cocaine.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Distances in the universe are enormous compared to those we are used to, so scientists use light years for measurement.  Approximately how many miles does a light year represent?", "correct_answer": "Six trillion miles", "incorrect_answers": ["Six zillion miles", "Six million miles", "Six billion miles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In mediaeval England, what was an ale-connor?", "correct_answer": "A beer-tester", "incorrect_answers": ["An unscrupulous merchant who sold muddy water flavoured with hops", "A wooden ale mug", "Ale seller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On December 3rd 1967, South African surgeon Christiaan Barnard succeeded in performing what?", "correct_answer": "The first human heart transplant", "incorrect_answers": ["The first brain operation", "The first lung transplant", "The first kidney transplant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1985 movie won the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 58th Academy Awards in 1986?", "correct_answer": "Out of Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["The Color Purple", "Prizzis Honor", "Witness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the book To Kill a Mockingbird?", "correct_answer": "Harper Lee", "incorrect_answers": ["James Baldwin", "Norman Mailer", "Mark Twain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A compass cannot be used on the Moon.  What factor is responsible for this?", "correct_answer": "Lack of a magnetic field", "incorrect_answers": ["Influence of Earths gravity", "Asteroid impacts", "Lack of gravity on the Moon"]}]